michaelcheney.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy — Michael Cheney

Last Updated: 24th May 2018

**1\. Introduction**

Seniority.co.uk Limited (the holding company of Michael Cheney) respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains in detail the types of personal information we may collect about you when you interact with us. It also explains how we will store and handle that personal information, how we keep it safe, how you can exercise your privacy rights and how we combine data across our business to help serve you better.

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, then please contact us at http://www.michaelcheney.com/support/

**2\. Who is Seniority.co.uk Limited?**

Seniority.co.uk Limited is the holding company of Michael Cheney - it is the umbrella organisation for all Michael Cheney's online businesses and products including, but not limited to, The Commission Machine, The 7-Figure Franchise, Commissionology, Commission Black Ops, Commission Cartel, Child's Play Profits, Fan Page Money Method, List Building Black Ops, Email Black Ops and Scope for Cash.

**3\. When do we collect personal information?**

We collect personal information in a number of instances, when you;

\- Buy one of our products through the JVZoo network  
\- Join one of our mailing lists by opting in with your email address  
\- Register for one of our webinars or training events  
\- Leave a voicemail for us on our Secure Order Processing Line  
\- Post a ticket on our Support Desk  
\- Reply to one of our emails  
\- Buy an affiliate product we recommend to you

**4\. What personal information do we collect and why?**

This falls into two clear categories;

Information You Give Us Voluntarily

When you buy one of our products through the JVZoo network you will enter your name and email address. We use this to create your membership account so you can access the program you bought.

When you join of our mailing lists by opting in with your email address we receive your email address and, depending on the page, sometimes your name too. We use this to correspond with you via email offering marketing promotions, special offers, trainings and so on. You can opt out at any time from some or all messages by clicking the unsubscribe link present at the bottom of every email.

When you register for one of our webinars or training events we receive your email address and, depending on the page, sometimes your name too. We use this to correspond with you via email about the webinar, give you your special registration link so you can attend and provide you free bonus training before the call as well as reminders after the call (where appropriate) to watch the replay or take advantage of the special offer which may be available. You can opt out of these emails by clicking the special link at the bottom of each email we send.

When you leave a voicemail for us on our Secure Order Processing Line you will of course leave personal information so we can process your order on our virtual terminal present via the PayPal interface. All of this information is strictly confidential and not stored in any way. It is instantly and permanently deleted the moment the transaction has been entered.

When you post a ticket on our Support Desk you will be asked to enter your name and email address. We use this to create your account at the Support Desk and send you email notifications about the status of your ticket.

When you reply to one of our emails you may provide us with information pertinent to your query. We use this to track down your order or assist you as best we can. This information is not stored or kept and is used solely to assist you with your query.

When you buy an affiliate product we recommend to you, you will have entered your name and email address to purchase the product. We occasionally provide you with additional free bonuses as a reward for purchasing the product and these are sometimes delivered via email and a special mailing list you are added to at the time you purchase the product. You may also, from time to time, receive marketing emails from us via this channel. As with all our email communications - you can stop them at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email.

**Information We Collect Automatically**

As part of running an online business there are aspects of data which are collected automatically due to the membership software and payment processing mechnisms we have in place.

When you buy one of our products, join any of our mailing lists, submit a support ticket or register for one of our webinars we will automatically receive your IP Address - this is your unique internet address associated with your internet service provider. We use this to prevent fraud by ensuring usernames and passwords for our paid products and not shared publicly. We also use the IP information occasionally as evidence of a user's identity in the event of PayPal claims and disputes.

Our autoresponder company (Getresponse) also retrieves general geographical information about you when you opt in based in your IP address. This is only detailed down to a regional / State level. We do not use this information for any purposes whatsoever - it's just something our autoresponder collects.

We also collect information related to your browser, operating system, computer type, web pages visited etc. Some of this information is collected via cookies. This information is used to anaylze website visitor behaviour and ensure our pages and trainings are viewable by as many people as possible.

**5\. Sharing Information**

We share only non-personal data with Google Analytics, Facebook, AdTrackz Split-Testing and JVZoo - see our Cookies Policy below for details.

**6\. Our Cookies Policy**

We only use cookies to serve you better. The four cookies we use are Google Analytics cookies, Split Testing cookies, Facebook cookies and JVZoo cookies.

The Google Analytics cookies enable us to track your usage of our websites and pages. They don't store any personal data and are used solely to track user behaviour across our websites.

The Split Testing cookies are used when we are running different tests on how well a certain web page or web element performs. This is so we can test out conversion rates and find the optimal results for our web pages. They don't store any personal data.

The Facebook cookies are used for retargeting ads on Facebook where we can run a Facebook ad targeting a user who has visited a specific page on our website. We don't see or control any personal data in this regard. We merely know that a user has visited a specific page - no personal information is received or stored by us in relation to this cookie.

The JVZoo cookies are used to ensure the correct referring affiliate is rewarded with the commission on the point of sale. We don't collect, see or have access to any private or personal data in regard to this cookie.

**7\. How Do We Keep Your Personal Data Safe and Secure?**

All data is stored on our own dedicated server protected with the latest anti-virus and anti-malware software and technology. All our sites have the secure SSL layer installed for added security and peace of mind.

**8\. Data Retention**

We retain all data on you when there is a business justification for doing so - i.e. you are an active subscriber, active member, active customer. If you are no longer active in our organization we will either delete, anonymize or secreuly store your data until which time it can be deleted. You may request deletion at any time of all data by posting a ticket on our Support Desk: http://www.michaelcheney.com/support/

**9\. Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We do make updates to this policy over time as our business and the internet technological landscape changes. When we do so we will try our utmost to notify you. Also please see the "Last Updated" date at the top of this document.

**10\. Your Data Protection Rights**

You have the following data protection rights:

If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by posting a ticket on our Support Desk: http://www.michaelcheney.com/support/

You can object to our usage of your data or seek to restrict it by contacting us also.

You can opt out from any or all of emails at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link present at the bottom of every email.

If you are not happy with our use of your personal data in any way please contact us below and we will seek to rectify it immediately.

**11\. How to contact us**

You can reach us by posting a ticket on our Support Desk: http://www.michaelcheney.com/support/
